[
  {
    "front": "あ",
    "back":  "a"
  },
  {
    "front": "い",
    "back":  "i"
  },
  {
    "front": "う",
    "back":  "u"
  },
  {
    "front": "え",
    "back":  "e"
  },
  {
    "front": "お",
    "back":  "e"
  },
  {
    "front": "か",
    "back":  "ka"
  },
  {
    "front": "き",
    "back":  "ki"
  },
  {
    "front": "く",
    "back":  "ku"
  },
  {
    "front": "け",
    "back":  "ke"
  },
  {
    "front": "こ",
    "back":  "ko"
  },
  {
    "front": "さ",
    "back":  "sa"
  },
  {
    "front": "し",
    "back":  "shi"
  },
  {
    "front": "す",
    "back":  "su"
  },
  {
    "front": "せ",
    "back":  "se"
  },
  {
    "front": "そ",
    "back":  "so"
  },
  {
    "front": "た",
    "back":  "ta"
  },
  {
    "front": "ち",
    "back":  "chi"
  },
  {
    "front": "つ",
    "back":  "tsu"
  },
  {
    "front": "て",
    "back":  "te"
  },
  {
    "front": "と",
    "back":  "to"
  },

  {
    "front": "な",
    "back":  "na"
  },
  {
    "front": "に",
    "back":  "ni"
  },
  {
    "front": "ぬ",
    "back":  "nu"
  },
  {
    "front": "ね",
    "back":  "ne"
  },
  {
    "front": "の",
    "back":  "no"
  },
  {
    "front": "は",
    "back":  "ha"
  },
  {
    "front": "ひ",
    "back":  "hi"
  },
  {
    "front": "ふ",
    "back":  "fu"
  },
  {
    "front": "へ",
    "back":  "he"
  },
  {
    "front": "ほ",
    "back":  "ho"
  },
  {
    "front": "ま",
    "back":  "ma"
  },
  {
    "front": "み",
    "back":  "mi"
  },
  {
    "front": "む",
    "back":  "mu"
  },
  {
    "front": "め",
    "back":  "me"
  },
  {
    "front": "も",
    "back":  "mo"
  },
  {
    "front": "や",
    "back":  "ya"
  },
  {
    "front": "ゆ",
    "back":  "yu"
  },
  {
    "front": "よ",
    "back":  "yo"
  },

  {
    "front": "ら",
    "back":  "ra"
  },
  {
    "front": "り",
    "back":  "ri"
  },
  {
    "front": "る",
    "back":  "ru"
  },
  {
    "front": "れ",
    "back":  "re"
  },
  {
    "front": "ろ",
    "back":  "ro"
  },
  {
    "front": "わ",
    "back":  "wa"
  },
  {
    "front": "を",
    "back":  "wo"
  },
  {
    "front": "ん",
    "back":  "n"
  },
  {
    "front": "が",
    "back":  "ga"
  },
  {
    "front": "ぎ",
    "back":  "gi"
  },
  {
    "front": "ぐ",
    "back":  "gu"
  },
  {
    "front": "げ",
    "back":  "ge"
  },
  {
    "front": "ご",
    "back":  "go"
  },
  {
    "front": "ざ",
    "back":  "za"
  },
  {
    "front": "じ",
    "back":  "ji"
  },
  {
    "front": "ず",
    "back":  "zu"
  },
  {
    "front": "ぜ",
    "back":  "ze"
  },
  {
    "front": "ぞ",
    "back":  "zo"
  },
  {
    "front": "だ",
    "back":  "da"
  },
  {
    "front": "で",
    "back":  "de"
  },
  {
    "front": "ど",
    "back":  "do"
  },
  {
    "front": "ば",
    "back":  "ba"
  },
  {
    "front": "び",
    "back":  "bi"
  },
  {
    "front": "ぶ",
    "back":  "bu"
  },
  {
    "front": "べ",
    "back":  "be"
  },
  {
    "front": "ぼ",
    "back":  "bo"
  },
  {
    "front": "ぱ",
    "back":  "po"
  },
  {
    "front": "ぴ",
    "back":  "pi"
  },
  {
    "front": "ぷ",
    "back":  "pu"
  },
  {
    "front": "ぺ",
    "back":  "pe"
  },
  {
    "front": "ぽ",
    "back":  "po"
  }
]
